[♪♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig. Snort.
This is
my little brother George.
Oink, oink.
This is Mummy Pig.
[SNORTS]
And this is Daddy Pig.
Peppa Pig. Snort.
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA:
"Cleaning the Car."
[GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig is taking the family
for a drive in the country.
Come on. Snort.
Is everybody ready?
Hee-hee-hee.
Ready!
Oink, oink.
Yes, Daddy Pig,
we're ready.
But the car
isn't ready.
Snort.
Look how messy it is.
Oh, it's not too bad.
You should see how messy it is
inside. Hee-hee-hee.
[GASPS]
Naughty, messy Daddy.
Hee-hee-hee.
[GIGGLES]
Look at all this rubbish.
Newspapers?
Snort. They're mine.
Sweets?
Snort.
They're mine.
Mr. Dinosaur?
Dine-saur. Grr!
Snort. We must clean the car
before we go for a drive.
Oh, right you are,
Mummy Pig.
Mummy, can we help
to clean the car?
Oink, oink.
Yes, if you want to.
Hooray!
Daddy Pig has some warm
soapy water to wash the car.
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho.
Daddy Pig is washing the roof.
[SNORTS]
Mummy Pig
is washing the bonnet.
[SNORTS]
Peppa is washing the doors.
Snort. Snort.
Hee-hee-hee.
George wants
to wash the windows,
but he is too little.
[CRIES]
Snort. Poor George.
Let me help you.
[GIGGLING]
[ALL LAUGH]
Oh, dear.
George has dropped his sponge
in a muddy puddle.
[SNORTS, GIGGLES]
PEPPA:
George.
You're making the car
all muddy again.
Oink.
[GIGGLES]
I will wash the mud off.
Peppa, don't use the--
Muddy water.
Oh, dear.
Peppa has thrown the muddy
water all over the car.
Oh.
Snort.
Never mind.
We can use the garden hose
to clean it off.
Yes, yes! Snort.
Can I hold the hose?
[GIGGLES]
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Snort. Snort.
[GIGGLES]
Peppa holds the hose
and Daddy Pig
turns on the water.
Snort. Where's the water?
[GURGLES]
Whaaa!
[GIGGLES]
Oh! Peppa, stop.
Sorry, Mummy.
[GIGGLES]
Oh.
Ah!
Daddy Pig, please
turn off the water.
Oh. Ha-ha-ha-ha.
No need to panic.
Oh, dear, everyone is wet.
Ho-ho-ho. At least
the car has been washed.
We've all been washed.
[ALL LAUGH]
You go and dry yourselves
while I polish the car.
See you later.
See you later. Snort.
Daddy Pig
is polishing the car so well
he can see his face in it.
[SNORTS, LAUGHS]
What a funny face.
Phbbt.
Oh, more funny faces.
It's Peppa and George.
Oh, ha-ha.
And Mummy Pig.
What a lovely
shiny car.
Yes, I am a bit
of an expert
at these things.
[ALL LAUGH]
Snort.
Come on, I'll drive today.
Is everybody ready?
MUMMY, GEORGE, PEPPA:
Ready.
Then let's go.
[HORN BEEPS]
Snort. I hope you will all
keep this car clean today.
Yes, Mummy Pig.
Oink, oink.
Oh!
Whoa!
Aah!
[GIGGLES]
Mummy, now you've made
the car all muddy again.
Ha-ha.
Naughty Mummy.
Hee-hee.
Naughty, messy Mummy.
[ALL LAUGH]
[ALL LAUGHING, SNORTING]
[HORN BEEPS]
PEPPA:
"Lunch."
Peppa and George have come
to Granny Pig and Grandpa Pig's
house for lunch.
Hee-hee-hee. Snort.
Granny Pig.
Oink. Ganggy Ig.
Hee-hee-hee.
Hello, my little ones.
Snort. Would you like
to pick some vegetables
from the garden for lunch?
Yes, please.
Oink.
[GIGGLING]
Grandpa Pig.
Baba Ig.
Snort.
Hello, Peppa, George.
This is Grandpa Pig's
vegetable garden.
He has grown
all these vegetables himself.
Grrr.
GRANDPA:
What's this?
Dine-saur.
A dinosaur? Ho-ho-ho-ho.
Snort. Let's choose
some vegetables for lunch.
[GIGGLES]
Peppa,
do you like tomatoes?
Snort. Yes, Grandpa Pig.
George, do you like tomatoes?
No.
George
does not like tomatoes.
Oh, dear.
Do you both like lettuce?
Snort. Yes, Grandpa Pig.
No.
Snort. George does not
like lettuce.
Oh, dear.
I must have something
that George likes.
Do you like cucumber?
Yuck.
George does not like cucumbers
and he does not like lettuce
and he does not like tomatoes.
Well, George,
what vegetable do you like?
Chocolate cake.
Hee-hee-hee.
Silly George.
Chocolate cake
isn't a vegetable.
Ho ho ho. Snort.
Maybe George
will like the vegetables
when they're made
into a lovely salad.
[GIGGLES]
Ohh, lovely fresh tomatoes,
lettuce and cucumber.
Snort.
First we have to wash them.
Peppa and George help
Granny Pig wash the vegetables.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
[LAUGHS]
Ha-ha-ha-ha. Snort.
Maybe that's enough washing.
Granny Pig
has made the tomatoes,
lettuce and cucumber
into a salad.
Grandpa Pig, can you
call everyone to lunch?
Lunch!
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Granny Pig has made pizza
for lunch.
And here's some salad made
with Grandpa's tomatoes,
lettuce and cucumber.
Tuck in, everyone.
[GOBBLING AND GRUNTING]
George has eaten his pizza,
but George does not like
the tomatoes
or the lettuce
or the cucumber.
Oh, dear, George.
Don't you like the salad?
No.
George,
just try a little bit
of this lovely tomato.
Yuck.
George, this is cucumber.
Grandpa Pig grew it
in his garden.
Bleah.
Try a piece of lettuce, George.
It's yummy.
[CRYING]
Now, now, George.
Look what I'm doing.
Now it's a dinosaur.
Oink. Dine-saur.
Hee-hee-hee. Grrr.
George loves dinosaurs.
George is eating the tomatoes,
lettuce and cucumber.
Well done, George.
Oink.
Would you like some more,
George?
Full.
George, are you too full
to eat any more tomatoes,
lettuce or cucumber?
Oink.
George is too full
to eat any more.
George, are you too full
to eat anything more?
Oink, oink.
George is too full
to eat anything more.
Oh, well, then you won't want
any of this chocolate cake.
Chocolate cake.
Oink, oink. Hee-hee-hee.
GRANDPA PIG:
My word.
George seems to have got
his appetite back.
[LAUGHING]
[GIGGLES]
PEPPA:
"Camping."
Peppa and her family
are going camping.
I love camping.
[SNORTS]
We're here.
PEPPA, GEORGE, MUMMY:
Hooray!
[GIGGLING]
Peppa, George,
this is the tent I had
when I was a little boy.
Daddy, how are you gonna
make that into a tent?
DADDY PIG:
Don't worry, Peppa.
I'm an expert at camping.
Snort.
Mummy Pig, put the tent
on the poles, please.
That's it.
Easy as pie.
Oh.
Do these pegs do anything?
Of course.
I forgot
about the pegs.
The pegs hold the tent up.
There.
Snort. The tent
is a bit little.
It was big enough for me
when I was a boy,
but it does look
a bit small now.
That's because
you've grown a bit
since you were a boy,
Daddy Pig.
And your tummy has grown
the most of all. Hee-hee.
Ho-ho-ho. Talking of tummies,
we should cook supper.
Yes, yes.
First we have to collect sticks
to make a fire.
Yipee!
Peppa and George
are helping Daddy Pig collect
sticks for the campfire.
George, I'll pick up the sticks,
and you can carry them.
Oink, oink.
[GIGGLING]
[GIGGLES]
Collecting sticks is fun.
Good.
That's enough sticks.
That's a splendid campfire.
Snort. Now I'll light it.
Here are the matches.
Ho-ho, we don't need matches.
Daddy, how can you light it
without matches?
I'm going to make fire
the old way,
by simply rubbing
these two sticks together.
Daddy Pig is rubbing
the two sticks together
to light the campfire.
Where is the fire,
Daddy?
Nearly there.
[BLOWS]
Hooray!
[WHEEZES]
Easy as pie.
[ALL LAUGH]
Snort. Now we can heat up
the tomato soup.
Ahh, listen
to the sounds of nature.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
What is that sound?
That is the sound
of crickets chirping.
[OWL HOOTS]
What is that?
That's an owl.
Look, there it is.
[HOOTS]
Wow.
Ohh.
[GURGLING NOISE]
And what's that noise?
Oh, I'm not sure.
[GURGLES]
It's Daddy's tummy.
[ALL LAUGH]
My tummy rumbling is one
of the best sounds of nature.
It means it's time to eat.
Snort.
I love tomato soup.
So do I.
[SLURPING]
Oh, there's another one
of Daddy Pig's
sounds of nature.
[BURPS]
Eh? What?
[ALL LAUGH]
Come on, children,
into the tent.
It's bedtime.
We won't all fit in.
The tent is too little.
It will be fine.
In you go.
Snort. Move further in,
Mummy Pig.
PEPPA:
Daddy, you're too big
for the tent.
Snort. Never mind.
I'd rather sleep
outside anyway.
Good night, Daddy Pig.
Good night,
Daddy.
Night. Night.
Good night, everyone.
Mummy Pig, Peppa and George
are sleeping in the tent.
Daddy Pig is sleeping outside,
under the stars.
Ahh. I love camping.
Sleeping in the open air
with the stars above me.
Maybe this wasn't such
a good idea after all.
Brr.
[ROOSTER CROWS]
It is morning.
Daddy, it was lovely and cozy
in the tent.
Oh, where's Daddy?
Daddy Pig has gone.
Poor Daddy Pig.
He must have been cold and wet.
And now where is he?
[SNORING]
What's that sound?
It sounds like snoring.
[PEPPA AND GEORGE GIGGLING]
[SNORING]
Hee-hee-hee.
Daddy Pig.
What?
Daddy, you're safe.
Ho-ho.
Of course I'm safe.
Snort.
I'm an expert at camping.
I slept in the car.
Hee-hee. Silly Daddy.
Ho-ho.
I love camping.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA:
"The Sleepy Princess."
It is night time.
Peppa and George
are going to bed.
[GIGGLING]
Good night,
Peppa and George. Snort.
Mummy? Daddy?
Yes, Peppa?
I'm not sleepy.
Can I have a story?
But maybe George is sleepy
and doesn't want a story.
George, do you want a story?
[SOFTLY]
Say yes.
Oink, oink.
Ho-ho-ho. Snort.
All right.
I will tell you
just one story.
Snort. If Daddy Pig
tells you a story,
you must both promise
to go to sleep.
We promise. Snort.
Oink, oink.
Hm. I think
I'll tell you the story
of "The Sleepy Princess."
Is it a good story?
It sounds a bit boring.
It's not boring.
It's very good.
Is there a little princess
in it?
Peppa, if you keep talking,
Daddy Pig can't start the story.
Sorry, Mummy.
Is there a little princess
in the story, Daddy?
Ho-ho.
Yes, there is
a little princess in it.
[SNORTS]
Oink, oink.
Hm. "The Sleepy Princess."
[♪♪♪]
DADDY PIG:
Once upon a time in a castle,
there lived
a little princess,
and she was called
the Sleepy Princess.
Daddy,
why was she called that?
I'll get to that later.
Was the Sleepy Princess
pretty?
Yes, she was very pretty.
She loved looking at herself
in the mirror.
I am so pretty. Snort.
Hee-hee-hee-hee.
Who else was living
in the castle?
Uh, well...
The others
in the castle were
the Small Prince...
Oink, oink.
Queen Mummy...
Snort.
...and King Daddy.
That's right. They were
all living there as well.
PEPPA:
Did King Daddy
have a big tummy?
Of course not.
He was very handsome.
Like me. Snort.
[GIGGLE]
Anyway,
there was also a dragon.
Dine-saur!
A dinosaur?
Oh, yes, it wasn't a dragon,
it was a dinosaur.
Living outside
was a huge fierce dinosaur.
Rawrrr! Rawrr-arr.
Rrawrrr!
[CRYING]
Oh, dear.
Maybe the dinosaur wasn't
quite that fierce, Daddy Pig?
Sorry, George.
No, the dinosaur
was very gentle.
It ate lots of grass.
[CRUNCHES]
[BURPS]
Daddy Pig.
Oop, sorry.
I was being the dinosaur.
[LAUGHS]
[GIGGLING]
Hee-hee-hee.
Daddy, why is the princess
called the Sleepy Princess?
I'm coming to that.
You see, the sun set,
then the stars and moon
came out,
and everyone got very sleepy.
[YAWNS]
But the most sleepy of all
was the Sleepy Princess.
[YAWNS]
Peppa, are you sleepy?
Snort. No, Daddy.
I am not sleepy at all.
[SNORING]
MUMMY PIG:
But somebody is.
George, wake up.
You'll miss the end
of the story.
Oink.
DADDY PIG:
Well, Peppa
might not be sleepy,
but the Sleepy Princess
certainly was.
Looking at herself all day
in the mirror
had completely worn her out.
[YAWNS]
Let's carry you to bed.
Snort.
Good night.
[SNORING]
The Sleepy Princess
was so sleepy,
she had fallen fast asleep.
[SNORING]
[SOFTLY]
Thank you for that story,
King Daddy.
[SOFTLY]
You're welcome,
Queen Mummy.
And our little prince
and princess enjoyed it too.
[SNORING, WHISTLING]
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA:
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTS, GIGGLES]
GEORGE:
Oink, oink.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTS]